<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Keith Hubner</title><link>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/</link><description>Recent content on Keith Hubner</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.143.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying Plausible to Civo Kubernetes</title><link>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/posts/deploying-plausible-civo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/posts/deploying-plausible-civo/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this guide, we will walk you through the process of deploying Plausible Analytics to a Civo Kubernetes cluster. Plausible Analytics is a lightweight and open-source web analytics tool that prioritizes privacy and simplicity. By the end of this tutorial, you will have a fully functional Plausible Analytics instance running on your Civo Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="prerequisites">Prerequisites&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before you begin, ensure you have the following setup:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Civo Account&lt;/strong>: A &lt;a href="https://www.civo.com/signup">Civo account&lt;/a> with access to create Kubernetes clusters.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Civo CLI&lt;/strong>: The &lt;a href="https://www.civo.com/docs/cli">Civo CLI&lt;/a> installed and configured on your local machine.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>kubectl&lt;/strong>: The &lt;a href="https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/tools/">Kubernetes command-line tool&lt;/a> installed and configured to interact with your cluster.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Helm&lt;/strong>: The &lt;a href="https://helm.sh/docs/intro/install/">Helm package manager&lt;/a> installed on your local machine.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Domain Name&lt;/strong>: A domain name that you can use for your Plausible Analytics instance.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Email Address&lt;/strong>: An email address to use for Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt SSL certificates.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>With these prerequisites in place, you are ready to proceed with the deployment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;strong>Keith Hubner&lt;/strong>, a tech enthusiast and software developer specializing in SaaS products, IT solutions, and retro gaming projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-i-do">What I Do&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Build technical IT solutions for various industries.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Design and develop SaaS applications.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Explore and share retro gaming ideas and projects.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="interests">Interests&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Networking and cloud computing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Open-source contributions.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Gaming and retro-inspired design.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Feel free to browse my projects and reach out!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/posts/deploying-plausible-to-civo-k8s/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keithhubner.github.io/keithhubner.com/posts/deploying-plausible-to-civo-k8s/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this blog post, we will explore how to deploy Plausible Analytics to a Civo Kubernetes cluster. Plausible is a lightweight and open-source web analytics tool that prioritizes privacy and simplicity. It provides website owners with essential insights without compromising user privacy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Civo is a cloud service provider that offers a developer-friendly Kubernetes platform. With its fast and efficient Kubernetes clusters, Civo makes it easy to deploy and manage containerized applications.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>